totalgovtjobs.com 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Total Govt Jobs 2013 | Sarkari Naukri 2013

**Privacy Policy @ Totalgovtjobs.com**

The privacy of our visitors is importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Totalgovtjobs.com and how it is used. 

**Third Party  Advertising:**

We use Google Adsense, Chitika, Infolinks, and other third-party advertising companies to servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.totalgovtjobs.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.totalgovtjobs.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.totalgovtjobs.com‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.totalgovtjobs.com

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.totalgovtjobs.com and other sites on the Internet.  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## Dont Forget to Join Us for Latest updates:

[**Through Email:**](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=totalgovtjobs) register your Email Id on this website, we will send latest updates in your mail inbox.  
[**Through Facebook:**](https://www.facebook.com/TotalGovtJobs) Like our FB Fan page for getting latest updates in your FB Timeline and share with your friends.  
[**Through Google +**](https://plus.google.com/100730346025134572493/posts) Share with your +1 Frieands
